

# Rok Jankovic

DATA SCIENTIST

rok.jankovic14@gmail.com

Alex Feldheimstraat 2, 1930 Zaventem, Belgium

0471 83 34 61

# SUMMARY

Data professional with 2 years of experience in analyzing, processing, and visualizing data and working experience in Python, SQL, and Power BI. During my professional career, I acquired solid experience in data engineering and data analysis. Moreover, I have experience in visualizing and modeling data in PowerBI.

## EDUCATION

2019-2021

MSc Quantitative Finance, WU Vienna, Vienna, Austria

2017-2018

(Erasmus Exchange) Finance, KU Leuven, Leuven, Belgium

2015-2019

BSc Economics,

University of Ljubljana, Ljubljana,

Slovenia

## SKILLS-

Data analysis: Python, R Visualization: PowerBl Data bases: SQL

Other: Airflow, Data Pipelines, ETL, ELT, PowerBI, Star Schema, Dax, Excel, MS office, ERP, VBA, Macros

#### LANGUAGES-

English: C2
Slovenian: C2
Croatian/Serbian: C2
German: B2
French: B1

## **EXPERIENCE**

02/2022 – Present

Zaventem, Belgium

Data Scientist - Personalization • Full Time • Samsung Jr. Data Scientist • Full Time • Samsung

07/2021 - 01/2022 (7 months)

Leuven, Belgium

Data Scientist • Temporary contract • AB InBev SA/NV

Data Scientist • Internship • AB InBev SA/NV

03/2020 - 03/2021 (13 months)

Vienna, Austria

Risk Analyst • Internship • Sberbank Eureope AG

03/2018 - 03/2019 (13months)

Ljubljana, Slovenia

Financial Analyst • Internship • NLB Skladi d.o.o.

# **Projects**

#### **Analytics Projects**

- Customer lifetime value (CLV) model,
- Propensity model,
- Segmentation using clustering,
- Media Mix Model

## **Data Engineering**

- Digital Media & Web Traffic ELT
- CRM ETL
- CRM Activation Platform (based on CLV)
- •

## Data Visualization

Digital Media Dashboard

## WEBSITE

To view some of my past analytics projects visit: https://rokuc.github.io/